{
    "question": "Apa jawaban darifrom of the following statements is true according to dhe to the advertisement above",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Apa jawaban dari pernyataan berikut ini yang benar menurut iklan di atas</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "edo-hello-im-in-airport-now-but-i-still-cant-find-your-311",
            "question": "Edo : Hello, I\u2019m in airport now. But I still can\u2019t find your sister. What does she look like? Dewi : She is tall. He has ... hair.\u00a0*    secepatnya yaaaaaa\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Brown/Black</p><p></p><p>Maaf kalau salah semoga menjadi jawaban terbaik ya :)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-yang-dimaksu-dengan-pantun-691",
            "question": "Apa yang dimaksu dengan pantun\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>Pantun adalah salah satu puisi lama yang baris pertama kedua merupakan sampiran dan baris ketiga keempat yaitu isi, mempunyai 4 baris, Setiap barisnya mempunyai 8-12 Kosakata (cara menghitungnya dengan cara dipenggal seperti, ayah: a-yah)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "rio-hello-dhika-what-time-do-you-usually-go-to-school-dhika-i-137",
            "question": "Rio Hello, Dhika. What time do you usually go to school?    Dhika :I go to school at six o'clock\r\nRio : Six o'clock? How do you go to school?\r\nDhika : I go to school by school bus\r\nRio Now. What kinds of things do you take to school?\r\nDhika : I usually take my backpack and books\r\nRio : okay. What is the first thing you do when you arrive at school?\r\nDhika we always greet our teachers and start our class with prayer\r\nRio : why do you usually study at school on Monday?\r\nDhika : we study English, civics, art and math\r\nRio : okay, where do you usually eat for lunch? Do you have lunchroom, canteen or cafeteria?\r\nDhika yes, there is canteen in my school\r\nRio now, what time do you usually go home?\r\nDhika : we sometimes go home at 3 o'clock\r\n1. What time does Dhika go to school?\r\nA. At six o'clock\r\nB. At seven o'clock\r\nC. At eight o'clock\r\nD. At a half six o'clock\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A. at six a clock</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p> semangat belajar nya ! </p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A. At six o&#039;clock</p><p></p><p>thanks</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "lirik-lagu-que-sera-sera-menjelaskan-tentang-ap-704",
            "question": "Lirik lagu que sera sera menjelaskan tentang ap??\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>kehawatiran seorang anak akan masa depannya</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Saat aku masih kecil</p><p>When I was just a little girl</p><p></p><p>Saya bertanya kepada ibu saya, saya akan menjadi apa?</p><p>I asked my mother, what will I be</p><p></p><p>Apakah saya akan cantik?</p><p>Will I be pretty</p><p></p><p>Apakah saya akan kaya?</p><p>Will I be rich</p><p></p><p>Inilah yang dia katakan padaku</p><p>Here&#039;s what she said to me</p><p>Que sera, sera</p><p>Que sera, sera</p><p></p><p>Apa yang terjadi terjadilah</p><p>Whatever will be, will be</p><p></p><p>Masa depan bukan milik kita untuk dilihat</p><p>The future&#039;s not ours to see</p><p></p><p>Que sera, sera</p><p>Que sera, sera</p><p></p><p>Apa yang akan terjadi terjadilah</p><p>What will be, will be</p><p>Saat aku dewasa dan jatuh cinta</p><p>When I grew up and fell in love</p><p></p><p>Aku bertanya pada kekasihku, apa yang ada di depan</p><p>I asked my sweetheart, what lies ahead</p><p></p><p>Akankah kita memiliki pelangi?</p><p>Will we have rainbows</p><p></p><p>Hari demi hari</p><p>Day after day</p><p></p><p>Inilah yang dikatakan kekasihku</p><p>Here&#039;s what my sweetheart said</p><p>Que sera, sera</p><p>Que sera, sera</p><p></p><p>Apa yang terjadi terjadilah</p><p>Whatever will be, will be</p><p></p><p>Masa depan bukan milik kita untuk dilihat</p><p>The future&#039;s not ours to see</p><p></p><p>Que sera, sera</p><p>Que sera, sera</p><p></p><p>Apa yang akan terjadi terjadilah</p><p>What will be, will be</p><p>Sekarang saya punya anak sendiri</p><p>Now I have children of my own</p><p></p><p>Mereka bertanya pada ibu mereka, aku akan jadi apa?</p><p>They ask their mother, what will I be</p><p></p><p>Apakah saya akan tampan?</p><p>Will I be handsome</p><p></p><p>Apakah saya akan kaya?</p><p>Will I be rich</p><p></p><p>Saya memberi tahu mereka dengan lembut</p><p>I tell them tenderly</p><p>Que sera, sera</p><p>Que sera, sera</p><p></p><p>Apa yang terjadi terjadilah</p><p>Whatever will be, will be</p><p></p><p>Masa depan bukan milik kita untuk dilihat</p><p>The future&#039;s not ours to see</p><p></p><p>Que sera, sera</p><p>Que sera, sera</p><p></p><p>Apa yang akan terjadi terjadilah</p><p>What will be, will be</p><p></p><p>Que sera, sera</p><p>Que sera, sera</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>ke kahawatiran se orang anak akn masa depan nya</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "2-menulis-minimal-5-kalimat-possitive-degree-ttg-benda2-di-rumah-544",
            "question": "2. Menulis minimal 5 kalimat possitive degree ttg benda2 di rumahmu.    3. Menulis minimal 5 kalimat comparative degree ttg benda2 di rumahmu\r\n 4. Pilih 5 pertanyaan d bawah ini, jawablah dengam kalimat superlative degree.\r\n Questions\r\n 1. Which flower has the most /the worst fragrance?\r\n 2. What is the longest/shortest river in the world?\r\n 3. Who is the heaviest/lightest man in the world?\r\n 4. Which is the smallest/biggest animal in the world?\r\n 5. Which animal does have the slowest/fastest movement?\r\n 6. What is the cheapest/the most expensive thing in the world?\r\n 7. What is the most popular activity during pandemic?\r\n 8. Who is the oldest man in the world?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>2. Menulis minimal 5 kalimat positive degree ttg benda2 di rumahmu.</p><p>a. My smartphone is <strong>as sophisticated as</strong> my laptop.</p><p>b. My car is <strong>as expensive as</strong> my uncle&#039;s car.</p><p>c. My bicycle is <strong>as new as</strong> my neighbor&#039;s bicycle.</p><p>d. My room is <strong>as clean as</strong> a hotel&#039;s room.</p><p>e. My books are <strong>as important as </strong>my professor&#039;s books.\n</p><p>3. Menulis minimal 5 kalimat comparative degree ttg benda2 di rumahmu</p><p>a. My laptop is <strong>more expensive than </strong>my smart phone.</p><p>b. My car is <strong>more expensive than</strong> my motorcycle.</p><p>c. My neighbor&#039;s bicycle <strong>is cheaper than</strong> my bicycle.</p><p>d. My room is <strong>more comfortable than </strong>a hotel&#039;s room.</p><p>e. My books are <strong>more important than</strong> my toys.\n</p><p>4. Pilih 5 pertanyaan d bawah ini, jawablah dengam kalimat superlative degree.\n</p><p>Questions\n</p><p>1. Which flower has the most /the worst fragrance?</p><p>I think Jasmine flowers have the <strong>most fragrance.</strong></p><p>I think Rafflesia Arnoldii has the <strong>worst fragrance.</strong>\n</p><p>2. What is the longest/shortest river in the world?</p><p>The Nile River is <strong>the longest</strong> river in the world.</p><p>The Roe River is <strong>the shortest</strong> river in the world.\n</p><p>3. Who is the heaviest/lightest man in the world?</p><p>Franco is <strong>the heaviest </strong>man in the world.</p><p>Junrey Balawing is <strong>the lightest</strong> man in the world.\n</p><p>4. Which is the smallest/biggest animal in the world?</p><p><strong>The biggest</strong> animal in the world is Antarctic Blue Whale.</p><p><strong>The smallest</strong> animal in the world is Etruscan shrew.\n</p><p>5. Which animal does have the slowest/fastest movement?</p><p>Cheetahs have <strong>the fastest</strong> movement of all animals.</p><p>Snails have <strong>the slowest</strong> movement of all animals.\n</p><p>6. What is the cheapest/the most expensive thing in the world?</p><p>A Lamborghini is <strong>the most expensive </strong>thing in the world.</p><p>Wheat is <strong>the cheapest</strong> thing in the world.\n</p><p>7. What is the most popular activity during pandemic?</p><p><strong>The most popular activity</strong> during pandemic is making contents on social media.\n</p><p>8. Who is the oldest man in the world?</p><p>Kane Tanaka from Japan is <strong>the oldest man</strong> in the world. He was born in 1903.</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p><strong>Rumus Degrees of Comparison:\n</strong></p><p><strong>\n</strong>Terdapat tiga tingkat perbandingan untuk kata sifat dan kata keterangan dalam bahasa Inggris, yaitu:\n</p><p>\nPositive degree\n</p><p>\nComparative degree\n</p><p>\nSuperlative degree\n</p><p>\nPositive degree digunakan untuk menyatakan sesuatu dalam keadaan selevel:\n</p><p>\nContoh : I am as happy as my parents. (Aku sebahagia kedua orang tuaku)\n</p><p>\n</p><p>Comparative degree dibentuk dengan menambahkan akhiran \"-er\"\n</p><p>\nContoh : Tony is younger than i am. (Tony lebih muda dariku)\n</p><p>\n</p><p>Superlative degree dengan menambahkan akhiran \"-est\" dan memiliki arti sebagai yang paling sehingga tidak bisa dibandingkan lagi.\n</p><p>\n</p><p>Contoh : I am the youngest person in my family. (Aku adalah orang termuda / yang paling muda di dalam keluargaku)\n</p><p>\nSemoga membantu ya.</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "you-have-asking-your-family-member-about-their-habit-533",
            "question": "You have asking your family member about their habit\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>kamu telah menanyakan ke keluargamu tentang hobi mereka</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "essays-1-give-2-examples-how-to-offering-help-2-what-is-narativ-333",
            "question": "Essays    1. Give 2 examples how to offering help\r\n2 What is \"Narative Text\r\n3. Write 2 sentences using \"should\r\n4. Name 2 examples of \"Quantifiers\"\r\n5 Give 1 sentence of \"Simple Past Tense\"\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. Hello,how could i help you?</p><p>   Hey,may i help you with something?</p><p>2.  . . .</p><p>3.You should go to bed now,Nathan.</p><p>   i think you should get some rest</p><p>4. . . .</p><p>5 . . .</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "make-sentences-with-the-words-given-1-seimpi-dance-traditional-165",
            "question": "Make sentences with the words given    1. Seimpi -dance-traditional\r\n 2.Mr.Handoko -teacher-kind\r\n 3. Miss kirana -dancer-famous\r\n 4. Jakarta-city-big\r\n 5. I-boy-strong\r\n 6.Farida-girl-slim\r\n 7. We-stundent-Indonesia\r\n 8. Borobudur-temple-famous\r\n 9. Indonesia-country-big\r\n 10. Wisnu-handsome-boy",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>1. Serimpi is one of the traditional dance from Yogyakarta.</p><p>2. Mr. Handoko is a kind teacher.</p><p>3. Mrs. Kirana is a famous dancer.</p><p>4. Jakarta is a big city.</p><p>5. I am a strong boy.</p><p>6. Farida is a slim girl.</p><p>7. We are Indonesian students / We are students from Indonesia</p><p>8. Borobudur is a famous temple.</p><p>9. Indonesia is a big country.</p><p>10. Wisnu is a handsome boy.</p><p></p><p>Penjelasan:</p><p></p><p>hope you find this helpful^\u2022^</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "quiz-sebutkan-rumus-simple-last-tense-no-ngasal-198",
            "question": "\u2b07QUIZ\u2b07\r\n\r\nSebutkan rumus simple last tense ! \r\n\r\nNo ngasal\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<h3><strong>V</strong><strong>erbal </strong></h3><ul><li>(+) S + Verb\u2082 + o/c</li><li>(-) S + did not/didn\u2019t + +Verb\u2081 + o/c</li><li>(?) Did + S + Verb\u2081 + o/c ?</li></ul><h3><strong>Nominal </strong></h3><ul><li>(+) S + to be (was/were) + Adj/Adv/Noun</li><li>(-) S + to be (was/were) + not + Adj/Adv/Noun</li><li>(?) To be (was/were) + S + Adj/Adv/Noun</li></ul><p></p><h2>Pembahasan</h2><p>Simple past tense adalah sebuah kata kerja yang digunakan untuk berbicara tentang aktivitas masa lalu. Simple Past sendiri biasanya menggunakan past verb/verb 2. Keterangan waktu yang biasa digunakan yaitu last week, last night, last month, last year, yesterday dsb.</p><p>  </p><h3>Contoh kalimat</h3><p><strong>Verbal</strong></p><ul><li>(+) She <strong>went</strong> to Jakarta yesterday</li><li>(-) She <u>didn&#039;t</u> go to Jakarta yesterday</li><li>(?) <strong>Did</strong> she go to Jakarta yesterday?</li></ul><p><strong>Nominal</strong></p><ul><li>(+) You <strong>were</strong> a student last year</li><li>(-) You <strong>were</strong> <u>not</u> a student last year</li><li>(?) <strong>Were</strong> you a student last year?</li></ul><p> </p><p> </p><h2>Pelajari lebih lanjut</h2><ul><li>1.rumus simpel past tense dan berikan 3 contoh kalitugas: <u>brainly.co.id/tugas/29713480</u></li><li>berikan 15 contoh simple past tense beserta positif, negatif dan interogatif ?? : <u>brainly.co.id/tugas/14440709</u></li><li>buatlah 5 kalimat past tense (+) (-) (?) : <u>brainly.co.id/tugas/24486587</u></li></ul><h2>Detail jawaban</h2><p>Kelas : 8</p><p>Mapel : Bahasa Inggris</p><p>Materi : Chapter 9 \u2014 Past tense</p><p>Kode Mapel : 5</p><p>Kode Kategorisasi : 8.5.9</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "read-the-dialog-and-answer-the-questions-number-2-to-4-onci-do-y-402",
            "question": "Read the dialog and answer the questions number 2 to 4.    Onci\r\nDo you know where Clara is?\r\nDafa She is in our school library. She went there with Ms. Nina, our school librarian, a few\r\nminutes ago\r\nOnci\r\nDafa\r\nWhat does she do in the library?\r\nShe helps Ms. Nina and Mr. Eko to check and arrange the books. She usually also helps the\r\nlibrary visitors to find some books. She always is in the library on Monday and Wednesday.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Kak pertanyaannya mana? ga bisa jawab</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}